[{"answer": "Leave!", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Should they say with the man or should they always believe him if he, abuses them?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Take me back, if you will, to the moment you came home and realized what was happening next door?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "I mean, that -- is that the reality of when you get caught in that kind of situation?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Yes, very well.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Did you know each other well?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "You know, well, she -- first of all, I think we just wanted to breathe.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "What was the first thing she said to you when you got to safety?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "You know, I appreciate it.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "What an incredibly -- is any there truth to rumors that you're thinking of wearing a cape now at work?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, I'm somebody that lives in the state of New Jersey where we don't have such a law.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What is your view, as a mayor of a big city in America, of the \"Stand Your Ground\" law?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "It was 1976, '75 or '76, when I started to really seriously love to go to Idaho, and \"Tapestry\" was 1971.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "When was that exactly?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I think it's just great.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What did you think of that moment then?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "I feel -- first of all, I am younger than all my daughters are now.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "When you sang that song like that, especially the way we just saw you singing there, when you look back at yourself there, knowing now what happened to your life then, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "You've been married four times now?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Third husband.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Third husband?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "No, it would be --", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "In your case, it'll be -- come on, how many dozen times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Did you marry every man you were properly in love with?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "If I could have trapped you on a desert island with one man in your life that you had a relationship with, who would it be?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Again, hope springs eternal.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Leave!", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "What do you say to women who watch this or who read the book, who find themselves in that position, should they stay with the man or should they always leave him if he -- they -- if he abuses her?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Thank you for getting that about me, because I don't have bitterness.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "It's a reflective book of someone who's had a pretty amazing life in many ways, haven't you?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "What would be the moment -- if I had the power to let you relive a moment in your life -- it can't be marriage, certainly not marriage in your case -- we'd be here all night.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "And if I can't, why be bitter?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Piers, I've had so many great moments, honestly.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "What's been the greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Oh God, I hope not.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "And on Thanksgiving and Christmas and stuff like that, is there a moment when the piano gets wheeled out?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I just keep all that separate.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, it's not my power.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Isn't that an amazing power to have, that you can do that through the power of music?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "ING: The other one, which I wrote -- I co-wrote with Ms. Tony Stern.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "What's the other song?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Sounds good.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "How does that sound?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "You know what, I always like to make the guest feel like they're the star, you know, contrary to public perception.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Were you really trying?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "It's an ego booster.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "So I think with you and Lionel, make you think you're better singers, it gives you more confidence?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Something like that.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "You've only sold what, 10 million albums?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Do you ever sing at home?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "But for fun?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I think there was a -- an instant the day I met him, 21 years ago, a connection there.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Was there a moment?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "We were.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Because you were good friends for a long time?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I don't know how to describe it.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "But if you've had so many years as friends, what's the moment like when suddenly you both realize it's going to be something else?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Of course, he was madly in love with me.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "He was must have been with you?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "You know a lot about that?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Is this even remotely healthy?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "I'm telling that you eat this and tomorrow you have a grape.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Is it just like a great, big, old fashioned southern pig out?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I'm a salt girl, so I would go for the chicken.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Which is your favorite of all this?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "That's sweet tea.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "What is this stuff?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "These are biscuits, basically.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "And what are these little cup cakes?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "So if I eat all of this, I would die, but with a smile on my face?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I packaged the meat later.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Did you do that?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "EARWOOD: Yes.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "How do you equate, though, this gorgeous food, which I would devoir in an instant, probably will the moment this interview is over, with the need in America, in particular, for people to probably eat less of this stuff?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Oh, sure.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Even as you're eating that stuff, are you quietly thinking fried chicken?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "It's why I keep doing it every single day.", "docId": "120413pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Daddy, is tonight movie night?", "qSentId": 698}]